{
    "id": "ba9f08f33c8e4101ac0fbf5a9185ee8d",
    "title": "Non-finites Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "............................ his lesson, he went out  to play cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Learnt",
                "Learning",
                "Having learnt"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4b1f0b4829fe49dba03e2906028cd898"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................... along the street one day, I saw a dead cobra.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Walked",
                "Walking",
                "Having walked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91265d92e22a4ff8b4610297f09aee71"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................... the forest we advanced into the open plain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Leaving",
                "Left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0657324c11ce41b4a86ea2e66d4fc61e"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ out of his country, he sought asylum in a foreign land.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Driving",
                "Driven",
                "Having driven"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3918114f7ada493a97e43dc1585d1267"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ........................... a very hot day, I remained in my tent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "being",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4ba9088a0c348a2a53093625079e544"
        },
        {
            "question": "A gipsy, ........................ across the meadows, found the child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wandering",
                "wandered"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7233d479b30c4abb826769466dfe8756"
        },
        {
            "question": "I once saw a man .......................... on a rope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "walking",
                "walked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a13beaa4bcfa444e91cbfff080553375"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not ........................ my way, I asked a policeman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knowing",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46484d27785e414c8e2c5ab4dc852734"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................ the noise, I woke up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "320bed5ef2ca407e983843ea04e86e89"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................ paralytic, he could not walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Being",
                "Having been",
                "Been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05cbfee7d2f8456285bc2221a588f0c3"
        }
    ]
}